HARIS MAHJOOB

Placentia, CA 92870

714-609-3397

harismahjoob42@gmail.com

SUMMARY OF QUALIFICATIONS

UCR graduate with a degree in Business Economics and a minor in Finance. Knowledgeable in data analysis programs and working on building a full-stack programming skillset. Able to design and create digital art using various software and technologies, and experienced in using various audio engineering software.

KEY SKILLS

- Trilingual: English, Farsi, Japanese
- · Word, Excel, PowerPoint
- · mySQL
- · JavaScript, CSS, HTML
- · NodeJS
- Photoshop
- Organizational Skills
- Leadership
- · Teamwork
- Communication Skills

EDUCATION

B.A. Business Economics - University of California Riverside, Riverside, CA

A.A. Economics - Fullerton College, Fullerton, CA

H.S. Diploma – Valencia High School, Placentia, CA

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

FRY'S ELECTRONICS

August 2014 - April 2015

Position: Sales Associate

 $\underline{Responsibilities} : Assisting \ customers \ with \ their \ purchases \ employing \ knowledge \ of \ computer \ products.$

PIZZA HUT

September 2015 – July 2019

Position: Delivery Driver

Responsibilities: Customer service, handling monetary transactions, delivering food via vehicle, preparing frozen food.

BALSEAL ENGINEERING

October 2021 - June 2022

Position: Automation Operator

Responsibilities: Managing automated machines used to manufacture springs and seals.